<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">
    <string name="AppName">Telegram Parsi</string>
    <string name="AppNameBeta">Telegram Parsi Beta</string>
    <string name="InviteText">"سلام، تلگرامیتی رو همین الان رایگان دانلود کن.
        لذت استفاده از تلگرام با اولین و سریع ترین کلاینت اندرویدی تلگرام با امکانات جذاب و بی نظیر!!

        * خواندن پیام ها به صورت نامحسوس
        * قفل اختصاصی
        * عدم نمایش آنلاین بودن (وضعیت نامحسوس)
        * فوروارد بی نام (بدون نقل قول)
        * تایپ کردن نامحسوس
        * آیدی یاب اختصاصی
        * تم بی نهایت رنگی
        * ترجمه روان و اختصاصی فارسی
        قابلیت های دیگه رو خودت تو برنامه ببین و استفاده کن!
        ____________________________
        اینم بگم که میتونی اونو کنار تلگرام اصلیت داشته باشی و نیازی نیست تلگرام رسمی رو پاک کنی و با این برنامه حتی میتونی دو تا شماره تلگرام رو گوشیت داشته باشی:
        http://bit.do/Invite2Telegram
        "
    </string>
    <string name="Passcode">Telegram Parsi Passcode Lock</string>
    <string name="ChangePasscodeInfo">When you set up an additional passcode, a lock icon will appear on the chats page. Tap it to lock and unlock your Telegram Parsi app.\n\nNote: if you forget the passcode, you\'ll need to delete and reinstall the app. All secret chats will be lost.</string>
    <string name="ChangePasscodeAlert">You will now see a lock icon on the chats page. Tap it to lock your Telegram Parsi app with your new passcode.</string>
    <string name="InviteUser">This user does not have Telegram Parsi yet, send an invitation?</string>
    <string name="Page1Title">Telegram Parsi</string>
    <string name="Page2Message"><![CDATA[<b>Telegram Parsi</b>]]> delivers messages faster than<![CDATA[<br/>]]>any other application.</string>
    <string name="Page3Message"><![CDATA[<b>Telegram Parsi</b>]]> is free forever. No ads.<![CDATA[<br/>]]>No subscription fees.</string>
    <string name="Page4Message"><![CDATA[<b>Telegram Parsi</b>]]> keeps your messages safe<![CDATA[<br/>]]>from hacker attacks.</string>
    <string name="Page5Message"><![CDATA[<b>Telegram Parsi</b>]]> has no limits on the size of<![CDATA[<br/>]]>your media and chats.</string>
    <string name="Page6Message"><![CDATA[<b>Telegram Parsi</b>]]> lets you access your messages<![CDATA[<br/>]]>from multiple devices.</string>
    <string name="Page7Message"><![CDATA[<b>Telegram Parsi</b>]]> messages are heavily encrypted<![CDATA[<br/>]]>and can self-destruct.</string>
    <string name="DrawerAdvancedSettings">Telegram Parsi Settings</string>
    <string name="IDHelp">You can find a username ID on <![CDATA[<b>]]>Telegram Parsi<![CDATA[</b>]]>. If you enter your desired username, click on the above checkmark in order to show the related profile.</string>
    <string name="CustomizationsHelp">Full management on your Telegram Parsi app\'s theme.\n\nNote: reopen the app to apply the changes.</string>
    <string name="AdvancedSecurityHelp">You can choose a passcode for your Telegram Parsi app, to protect the messages from stranger\'s access.</string>
    <string name="ChangeFontAlertMessage">Are you sure to change the Telegram Parsi font? Needs to restart the app for applying the changes.</string>
</resources>